yeah
是的
thank you dear I will do it in English
谢谢你，亲爱的我会用英语
because there are some people who do not
因为有些人不
understand German and the first session
了解德语和第一节课
was in English already you are the
已经是英文了，你就是
exception so so what I learned in the
例外，所以我从中学到的
five minutes is the German cinemas doing
五分钟是德国电影院
so bad then now we have Java in cinema
太糟糕了，现在我们在电影院里有了Java
and Java is doing so well that all
Java做得很好，
magazines are free right so Java
杂志是免费的，所以Java
supports German cinemas right this is a
支持德国电影院，这是一个
quality content I would say right with
我会说正确的高质量内容
agile and are he taking whatever so this
敏捷，他是否正在采取一切措施
is true this is going to be a keynote
是的，这将成为主题演讲
and in the airplane yesterday I actually
昨天我在飞机上
planned to heck the whole time and but
计划整天整顿，但是
this wouldn't be a keynote as I will
这不是我的主题演讲
heck something they are to show you that
弄些他们要告诉你的东西
it actually even works but I prepared
它实际上甚至可以工作，但是我准备了
some slides and translate them to
一些幻灯片并将其翻译为
English now so first about I am
现在是英文，所以关于我
freelancer working with Java since 1995
从1995年开始使用Java的自由职业者
and the strange thing is I really like
奇怪的是我真的很喜欢
it still and I don't try even you know
它仍然，即使您知道，我也不会尝试
to be a manager whatever I just like
成为经理，无论我喜欢什么
hacking so I really enjoy that and I'm
黑客，所以我真的很喜欢，我
not really interested in Scala code
对Scala代码不是很感兴趣
Linden or whatever so I do JavaScript
Linden或其他使我执行JavaScript的人
and Java I'm very happy so could be that
Java我很高兴，所以可能
which car would make me happier but I
哪辆车会让我更快乐，但我
don't think so
不要这样
so um I don't have so much time to
所以我没有太多时间
compile this is the problem right so um
编译这是正确的问题，所以嗯
what I do are the most interesting part
我所做的是最有趣的部分
is the ax of M this is a podcast why are
是M的斧头，这是播客，为什么
doing this because usually I have no no
这样做是因为通常我没有
time at conferences to speak with
在会议上与之交谈的时间
interesting people so what I did is I
有趣的人，所以我所做的就是我
started like the podcast and there's
开始像播客，
like one hour conversation I was curious
像一个小时的谈话，我很好奇
about micro profiles I interviewed Emily
关于我采访艾米丽的微观概况
right so we did a podcast stand up so
对，所以我们做了一个播客，所以
the she's like the micro profile guru
她就像微调大师
and asked all question interests me and
并问了所有我感兴趣的问题
the most interesting podcast for today
今天最有趣的播客
as well is Mike building Kovac he's from
迈克还在建造他来自的科瓦奇
Eclipse Foundation asked hard questions
Eclipse Foundation提出了难题
about her heart for me interesting
关于她的心对我很有趣
questions about Jakarta a e4j and all
有关雅加达a e4j和所有的问题
the chaos from last year and now I
从去年到现在的混乱
understand everything and I try to
了解一切，我尝试
translate it to you as well so some
也把它翻译给你
workshops on the immunity Airport and
关于豁免机场的讲习班和
this is my so this was like in Ooty one
这是我的，所以这就像乌塔卡蒙德
second
第二
where you know whatever you saw this is
你知道你看到的是什么
like no black magic but now why I'm
喜欢没有黑魔法，但为什么我现在
still saying I hope LAN wan to
仍然说我希望局域网
never-never my great so I didn't
从来没有我的伟大，所以我没有
actually wanted to learn all the fancy
其实想学所有的幻想
frameworks for the beginning I just
我刚开始的框架
stick with the middle and the
坚持中间和
interesting part is 80% of left and
有趣的部分是剩下的80％
right left and right of the middle just
左右中间的左右
died in the last 20 years so I didn't
在过去的20年中去世，所以我没有
have to ruler and everything every two
必须统治，一切每两个
days and this is probably why I still
天，这可能就是为什么我仍然
enjoy that and the same happens now in
享受那个，现在同样发生
the web so in web I do the same so just
网络，所以在网络中，我也一样
try to delete frameworks and be happy
尝试删除框架并开心
so now start with Java 7l if you have
所以现在开始使用Java 7l
any questions just ask me it should be
任何问题只是问我应该是
interactive so this is the first slide
互动的，所以这是第一张幻灯片
with content which I had to translate
我必须翻译的内容
from German to English so that's the
从德语到英语，这就是
first one Java is seven or eight so last
第一个Java是七个或八个，最后一个
year Java 8 came out and I got lots of
年Java 8诞生了，我有很多
lots of questions interviews two years
两年面试的很多问题
before or even three what's my feeling
甚至三点之前我有什么感觉
that Java is late late and I said okay I
Java迟到了，我说好吧
have to admit I have complete different
必须承认我完全不同
problems in project it's not like people
项目中的问题不像人
missing new api's it's more like you
缺少新的api更像你
know they exaggerate with the existing
知道他们夸大了现有的
api's so I'm talk a little bit in the
api，所以我在
next session about that but it seems to
下届会议有关，但似乎
me like you know insurance companies are
我就像你知道保险公司
not that interested in selling
对销售没有兴趣
insurances and more like in mapping
保险，更喜欢映射
layers or data transfer objects or data
层或数据传输对象或数据
access objects or whatever they can do
访问对象或它们可以做什么
just not to touch the business logic so
只是不要触碰业务逻辑
this was my problem in my projects okay
这是我项目中的问题
for the marketing Java e8 is great but
对于市场营销Java e8很棒，但是
it's not like we will speed up you know
并不是说我们会加快你的速度
all projects by 30%
所有项目减少30％
so this was my personal view which was
所以这是我的个人观点
not that popular but Java 8 came out
不是那么流行，但是Java 8出现了
they were really happy with that so I'm
他们真的很高兴，所以我
and the same on the same level on this
并在同一级别上
around the same time there was Java one
大约在同一时间有Java
last year this was a thing October
去年十月
and with around Java 7 I got a call with
在Java 7左右，我接到了一个电话
I think it was it was people from payara
我认为那是帕亚拉人
with people from Red Hat and they asked
和来自Red Hat的人一起，他们问
what should we do about an activity of
我们应该怎么做的活动
Oracle so we could try try to do
甲骨文，所以我们可以尝试做
something and call it micro profile and
并称其为微型个人资料，
I'll say ok we could do something but
我会说好的，我们可以做点什么，但是
actually Java 7 works like yeah but then
实际上Java 7的工作原理是
we could move faster and um so my my my
我们可以移动得更快一些，所以我是我的我
opinion about micro profile was in the
关于微轮廓的意见在
first I would say 1 to 2 years
首先我会说1至2年
superfluous stuff just for marketing so
多余的东西只是为了营销所以
if someone would like to play with no 2
如果有人想玩没有2
makes less jar and and be happy that the
使罐子减少，并为
application server takes in production
应用服务器开始生产
to kilobyte less ram they should do
要减少千字节的内存
micro profile and then play a little bit
微型个人资料，然后播放一点
more with the technology so about one
技术带来更多的好处
half year ago what I completely missed
半年前，我完全错过了
and didn't recognize back Dennis that
并没有认出丹尼斯
most application servers stock
大多数应用服务器库存
application servers we already have
我们已经拥有的应用服务器
support both Java 8 and micro profile
同时支持Java 8和Micro Profile
and this changed my opinion completely
这完全改变了我的看法
because then I can actually use micro
因为这样我才能真正使用微型
profile right now in most application
现在在大多数应用程序中配置文件
servers without changing anything and
服务器无需更改任何内容，
that's changing anything this what I
这改变了我的一切
like in projects I don't like to come in
就像在项目中我不喜欢进来
fact look delete everything we introduce
事实上看起来删除了我们介绍的所有内容
a new framework everything is going to
一个新的框架，一切将要
be better and after half year do the
会更好，半年后
same you know instead of request
你知道而不是要求
response framework then reactive
然后反应框架
framework or whatever framework you get
框架或您得到的任何框架
in two years so but something will
在两年内
always happen you always will find a
总是发生，你总是会找到一个
reason not to focus on business logic
不关注业务逻辑的原因
right so now and in the podcast was
所以现在和播客中
Emily what also interesting so you have
艾米莉（Emily）还有什么有趣的事
four releases in a year which is
一年中有四个版本
incredible so we get four read releases
令人难以置信，所以我们得到了四个阅读版本
three Dedede Cadence's extremely fast
三个Dedede Cadence的速度非常快
and they are very very pragmatic at the
他们在这方面非常务实
same time or at the same time a little
同一时间或同一时间
bit length later was one year before so
有点长才过了一年
it was October 2017 I got I was I think
那是2017年10月我明白了
was before Java one order H other one
在Java之前一个命令H另一个
there was like a fo J's is out an Oracle
就像fo J出了甲骨文一样
open sources
开源
Java EE
Java EE
and call his efore James like Evo Jade
并像Evo Jade那样称呼他的前詹姆斯
they're crazy and why because before I
他们疯了，为什么，因为在我之前
did some code reviews and this was the
做了一些代码审查，这是
same story log4j simple log4j but no
相同的故事log4j简单的log4j但没有
business logic just logging
只是记录业务逻辑
configuration caching and mapping and
配置缓存和映射以及
one class which does something this was
一类这样做的东西是
my well and then Oracle came out MIDI
我很好，然后Oracle发出MIDI
for Jade another for J just stupid name
为玉又为J只是愚蠢的名字
I hate it so I o'clock for j SL for J in
我讨厌它，所以我将J SL替换为J in
the e fo j and what turn out this evo J
e fo j和结果是什么evo J
name really does not matter at all and
名称真的根本没有关系，
this is what I was not clear to me at
这是我不清楚的
all and also wasn't clear at all how
所有，也根本不清楚
eclipse operates because what I didn't
蚀之所以运作，是因为我没有
like it eclipse is the Eclipse IDE why I
喜欢它的原因Eclipse IDE是我为什么
didn't like that
不喜欢那样
yeah because was the same where you go
是的，因为你去的地方都一样
to the page you get 50 IDs and you
到该页面，您将获得50个ID，而您
actually would like only to create a
实际上只想创建一个
small Java projects and you will ask you
小型Java项目，您会问你
would you like to have a clip some for
您想要一个剪辑吗
Model S for testers or I don't know for
适用于测试人员的Model S还是我不知道
cookus or for whatever for astronomist
炊具或任何天文学家
and as I know I would just take some
据我所知，我会带一些
code and now this was the toast of the
代码，现在这就是
question to Mike it's like I don't like
问迈克，就像我不喜欢
you know to end up with Java like in
你知道最终会像
eclipse where if you would like to have
蚀在哪里，如果你想
a profile for I don't know for crowd I
我不知道的个人资料
get three less classes and a profile for
少上三堂课
WebSocket I get five more classes and
WebSocket我又得到了五个类
it's safe you know two cents in
你知道两分钱是安全的
production because I save half RM of
生产，因为我节省了一半的RM
memory and questions so far so what it
记忆和问题至今如何
turn out this Evo J doesn't matter this
原来这个Evo J没关系
is like name of the container of all
就像所有容器的名称
projects of the implementation and no
项目的实施与否
one actually talks about foj and Noah
有人在谈论福伊和诺亚
will see for J in the source code what
会在源代码中看到J
is a good thing the question is what is
一件好事，问题是什么是
the Jakarta EE
雅加达EE
and this Jakarta is this what Eclipse
这个雅加达就是Eclipse
doesn't have so this is my understanding
没有，这是我的理解
eclipse ID on has the e4j but there is
eclipse ID上有e4j，但是有
no Jakarta account apart and what did
没有雅加达账户，做什么了
Jakarta he is is like the brand and this
雅加达他就像品牌一样
is unique also unique told me that this
独特也独特告诉我，这
is like the JCP of Jakarta and and
就像雅加达的JCP和
people and and the decadence of foj and
人与佛吉的the废和
Jakarta could be even different so we
雅加达可能会有所不同，所以我们
could have 50 releases of e4j and only
可能只有50个版本的e4j
one release of Jakarta this was
雅加达的一个版本是
absolutely not clear to me
我绝对不清楚
so the next question was okay nice but
所以下一个问题很好，但是
let's say I have a great idea and I
假设我有一个好主意，而我
would like to start my new you know my
想开始我的新事，你知道我的
new logging framework I would like to
我想要的新的日志记录框架
have my logging beam for J let's say in
我有J的测井光束
e4 j how to do this and they say okay
e4 j如何做到这一点，他们说还可以
this is actually pretty easy I have to
这实际上很容易
to start up a new project applied in the
开始一个新的项目
pmc and if it's a good enough is going
pmc，如果足够好的话
to be taken and how it usually works in
以及通常如何使用
for J is you have to become a committer
因为J是您必须成为提交者
and if you are a committer this is our
如果您是提交者，这就是我们的
way to do this you have to contribute in
方法，你必须贡献
one point of time the other committers
一个时间点，其他提交者
will say it is cheaper to make your
会说让你的便宜
committee I don't have to review changes
委员会，我不必审查更改
and then you become a committer and if
然后您成为提交者，如果
you are a committer you have a vote and
您是提交者，您有投票权，
with the vote you can vote against the
您可以投票反对
others so this is how this is
其他人，这就是这样
transparent how Jakarta Eve works and
透明雅加达前夕的工作方式以及
this is perfect for me why because I was
这对我来说是完美的，为什么因为我
really concerned was the whole Jakarta
真正关心的是整个雅加达
you can follow my mailing lists my mails
你可以按照我的邮件列表我的邮件
in the Jakarta community because the
在雅加达社区，因为
mailing and what I learned is the
邮寄，我学到的是
mailing list doesn't have any and
邮件列表没有任何内容，
anything to say so they can it they can
有话要说，所以他们可以做到
dream about whatever they they do they
梦见他们所做的一切
are not commit as usually which is a
不像平常那​​样提交
very good thing why because from day one
很好的原因为何，因为从第一天开始
they try to introduce more profiles
他们尝试介绍更多个人资料
which I really hate it so what I like in
我真的很讨厌它，所以我喜欢
Java eat the most or Jakarta or micro
爪哇人吃得最多还是雅加达或微型
profile you get one thing one dependency
配置文件，你得到一件事，一个依赖
and you start your project so I don't
你开始你的项目，所以我不
like another huge investigation at the
就像在
beginning which micro profiles might be
开始哪些微资料可能是
interested in my thing
对我的东西感兴趣
I would like to have everything at once
我想一次拥有一切
and fast and start hacking and it seems
并快速开始黑客攻击，看来
like it will remain the same because the
希望它会保持不变，因为
whole jakarta ii profiles will have to
整个雅加达ii配置文件将不得不
be decided by the jakarta a committee
由雅加达委员会决定
and therefore and therefore it is not
因此，因此不是
like someone will get an idea on the
就像有人会想到
mailing list and we get new profile ok
邮件列表，我们会获得新的配置文件
so we are safe so it will somehow like
所以我们很安全，所以它将以某种方式
Jakarta Jakarta
雅加达雅加达
you can call it monolithic which I like
你可以称之为我喜欢的整体式
why because I show you how monolithic is
为什么，因为我向您展示了整体性
this a little bit in source code and the
这一点在源代码和
micro profile is similar you have we
微型个人资料与您相似
have two old version I think right now
我现在有两个旧版本
out or even two
甚至两个
- OH tire already already supports oven
-OH轮胎已经支持烤箱
Liberty a think supports - oh and what I
自由思想支持-哦，还有我
use in productions one three but I don't
在生产中使用三分之一，但我不
care no that I just would like to have
不在乎我只是想拥有
open API or open tracing I don't care
我不在乎开放的API或开放的跟踪
about that I would like to have the
关于我想拥有
whole thing I'm using open API or sorry
我正在使用开放式API的全部或抱歉
micro Profi 201 3 and absolutely not
micro Profi 201 3绝对不是
interested just having let's say fault
有兴趣只是说错
tolerance but not the config I don't
宽容但不是我不喜欢的配置
care I would have to have all why
照顾我必须拥有所有的原因
because of speed so micro profile we
由于速度如此微细，我们
covered that what is the relation about
涵盖了关于什么的关系
Jakarta Yi and micro profile my
雅加达易和微个人资料我
Impressionist jakarta ii people would
印象派雅加达二世人会
like to have micro profile integrated
喜欢整合微轮廓
and I would say it would be probably not
我会说可能不是
that smart because micro profile
这么聪明，因为微简介
iterates very quickly they are
他们很快地迭代
independent and how it is look right now
独立以及现在的样子
it is perfect I would say and if they
我会说这是完美的，如果他们
will integrate to Jakarta eat they will
将融入雅加达吃他们会
probably slow down the whole micro
可能会减慢整个微观
profile which would be a bad thing and
个人资料，这将是一件坏事，
right now if you consider a health check
现在，如果您考虑进行健康检查
for instance API there are few classes
例如API的类很少
it was created by by I think a team of
它是由我认为由
two or even one guy created this and and
两个甚至一个人创造了这个
n is done questions there's the future
回答问题是否存在未来
of enterprise we have this and and by
企业我们有这个
the way pivotal Microsoft everyone is
关键的微软所有人的方式是
part of Jakarta e ok and how and how it
雅加达e ok的一部分以及如何以及如何
happened I was curious what was the
碰巧我很好奇
process and there was one manager Oracle
过程中，只有一位经理Oracle
he's no more a terrible Oracle could be
他不再是一个可怕的甲骨文
the reason but I don't know Markovic and
原因，但我不知道Markovic和
he pinked mike and said we would like to
他把迈克粉了一下，说我们想
do something with java do you have time
用Java做点事吗
to talk and they met and now now they
交谈，他们见了面，现在他们
got jakarta
雅加达
they got fo g started evo J now the name
他们开始了evo J的名字
Jakarta is brilliant I really like that
雅加达很棒，我真的很喜欢
every other names were just terrible
所有其他名字都太糟糕了
Enterprise Java for something here who
企业Java在这里有谁
cares but Jakarta is great because we
在乎，但雅加达很棒，因为我们
had Jakarta Apache dot orc a piece of
雅加达的Apache点兽人
Java history there was the Tomcat stuff
Java历史上有Tomcat的东西
was a part of Jakarta and Apache don't
是雅加达的一部分，而Apache不
donated the Jakarta to eclipse so now
捐赠了雅加达使其黯然失色
than Jakarta is official and the logo is
比雅加达是官方的，徽标是
great I forgot to show you the logo but
太好了，我忘了给你看徽标，但是
you have the logo right you have to show
您拥有必须显示的徽标权利
us this it looks like a sailing boat
我们这看起来像帆船
with something right so and the idea of
正确的想法和
Jakarta came from David Blevins right
雅加达来自大卫·布列文斯（David Blevins）
from Tomy is it true
来自Tomy是真的
here the idea and David Blevins Esther
这里的想法和大卫·布列文斯·以斯帖
behind open e gb and and tummy which is
背后打开e gb和肚子是
a very small as small as open liberty
和自由一样小
application server so this is now
应用服务器，所以现在
history so and i would rise to clarify
历史如此，我将澄清
that because i seems like there's a lots
那是因为我好像有很多
of confusion going on what it actually
混乱到底在发生什么
is
是
any questions everyone crystal clear
任何问题大家都清楚
perfect
完善
so foj killed jakarta a lives so this is
所以foj杀死了雅加达一个人的生命，所以这是
what matters and we get release I guess
重要的是我们得到释放
end of year it's planned to have a
计划到年底
release now the question is why it takes
现在发布，问题是为什么需要
so long and because the scope is larger
这么长，因为范围更大
by the way this is the one of the
顺便说一下，这是其中之一
largest projects on Eclipse
Eclipse上最大的项目
why is larger because what I do right
为什么更大，因为我做对了
now is they create a CI CD transparent
现在是他们创建透明的CI CD
Jenkins pipelines for each project which
詹金斯为每个项目准备的管道
were not existing before and they say
以前不存在，他们说
this is part of the project we have the
这是我们拥有的项目的一部分
transparency they migrate the whole TCK
透明，他们迁移了整个TCK
which is not part official part of Java
这不是Java的官方部分
EE distributions now part of Jakarta and
EE发行版现已成为雅加达和
this is a lot of work so if you have
这是很多工作，所以如果您有
time contributes you can do really hey I
时间贡献你真的可以做我
would like to help you with the pipeline
希望对您有所帮助
and you can do it
你可以做到
so not another problem is completely
所以没有另一个问题是完全
open community and they would like to
开放社区，他们想
have some help so questions so after the
有一些帮助，所以提出问题后
show
节目
create some pipelines and they are happy
建立一些管道，他们很高兴
so and this is marketing yeah this is if
所以这是行销是的，如果
you would like to come to Munich there
你想来慕尼黑
are workshops and over here now setup
是工作室，现在在这里设置
Java project and let's call it Jake on
Java项目，我们称其为Jake
and what it is is this is how I start my
这就是我开始我的方式
projects and because I do it's often
项目，因为我经常这样做
said regions I don't know what the
说地区我不知道
devious setup a java project so and I
vious回设置一个Java项目，所以我
will show you this is just maven
会告诉你这只是行家
archetype can't so and you can use it in
原型不能如此，您可以在其中使用它
IDE in I have to build NetBeans of
我必须在IDE中构建NetBeans
course and envisions with your code or
课程和设想与您的代码或
whatever and because I will show you
随便，因为我会告诉你
that other works without IDE and what I
其他没有IDE的作品，我
do usually not very conferences I
我通常不会开会
usually usually use some scripts and now
通常通常使用一些脚本，现在
call it jquan and if the internet is
称它为jquan，如果互联网是
working as setup Java project and call
用作安装Java项目并调用
it jquan so now the project hopefully is
它是jquan，所以现在希望该项目是
going to be created it tries to pull the
将要创建它试图拉
dependencies from maven central not
来自Maven Central的依赖关系
Apache central maven central and now I
Apache Central Maven Central，现在我
need an IDE
需要一个IDE
I was asked before the show which ID I'm
演出前有人问我我是哪个ID
using I'm I'm using right now still
我现在正在使用
NetBeans because I only need maven but I
NetBeans，因为我只需要Maven但我
also use more and more Visual Studio
也使用越来越多的Visual Studio
code I still try to avoid a little bit
代码我还是尽量避免一点
eclipse and I like IntelliJ the problem
蚀，我喜欢IntelliJ的问题
is the shortcuts are just crazy and the
捷径是疯狂的，
initial setup is like it cannot explain
初始设置就像无法解释
anyone how to set up application server
任何人如何设置应用程序服务器
in IntelliJ but if it runs it runs but
在IntelliJ中，但如果运行，它将运行，但是
then you forget it again what it
然后你又忘记了它
actually did and and and and people ask
确实做了and和and and人们问
me can you show me you just would like
我可以告诉我你只是想
to deploy once to payara and I couldn't
一次部署到payara，我不能
and I say you you you talk how easy Java
我说你，你说Java多么容易
is and they cannot even set up the
是的，他们甚至无法设置
servers again IntelliJ I can show you
服务器再次IntelliJ我可以告诉你
how to do command-line bonatelli J is a
怎么做命令行bonatelli J是一个
different story ok so now what I mean by
不同的故事好吧，现在我的意思是
simple so now I switch to junk workspace
很简单，所以现在我切换到垃圾工作区
and it will recognize hopefully there's
它将希望认识到
a project jquan and this is also put I
项目jquan，这也把我
need and
需要和
so and this is Java age project and
所以这是Java时代的项目，
usually what I do always is all my
通常我所做的总是我所有的
projects right now no kidding are that
现在的项目不是在开玩笑
so one three two oh not yet but I will
一三二哦，但我会
start with two Oh with payara five and I
从两个哦开始，与薪pay五和我
will use today payara I could use white
今天将使用payara我可以使用白色
fly and next week I'm using open Liberty
飞，下周我将使用开放自由
for a startup there's a better fit for
对于初创公司来说，更适合
open Liberty so if the conference would
开放自由，以便会议召开
be one week later I would switch to
一个星期后，我会切换到
openly but it's the problem is I don't
公开地，但是问题是我没有
have like conference lot laptop
有像会议笔记本电脑
everything is set up with spire and
一切都由尖顶和
white fly so it's a little bit of risk
白蝇，所以有点风险
now to show you open Liberty because I
现在向您展示开放自由，因为我
don't know then try it for few weeks
不知道然后尝试几个星期
okay
好的
so huh yeah she will show you open
所以是的，她会告诉你打开
Liberty and what I can tell you is open
自由，我能告诉你的是开放的
Liberty right now is one of the best and
现在的自由是最好的之一，
this is a it is I would call it it's
这是一个我会称之为的
like the next generation of WebSphere
像下一代的WebSphere
because it is you shouldn't mention
因为那是你不应该提及
websley at all in if you open is it the
如果您打开websley，是不是
smallest startup is the fastest and very
最小的创业公司是最快的
pragmatic configuration so this one can
务实的配置，所以这可以
tell you about open Liberty it's
告诉你开放的自由
completely open source right now and you
现在完全开源，您
can buy without any problems support
可以毫无问题地购买支持
from from IBM why I know that because I
来自IBM的原因为何我知道，因为我
was curious and did a podcast with Erin
很好奇，和艾琳做了一个播客
Schnabel and she is the what was it she
施纳贝尔和她是什么她
she was one of the open Liberty
她是开放的自由女神之一
architects architects and so I asked her
建筑师，所以我问她
her hard questions and what interests me
她的难题和什么让我感兴趣
for my clients if I just download open
对于我的客户，如果我只是下载open
Liberty can i buy support yes or no and
我可以自由购买支持吗？
you can if you like if no don't buy it
如果愿意，可以的话就不要买
yeah but it's got the information show
是的，但是有信息显示
of Buicks ago so you can buy the support
的价格，所以您可以购买支持
for open Liberty but you don't have to
开放的自由，但您不必
so and there's no limitations no like
所以没有限制没有像
yeah okay you have for IBM actually
是的，您实际上对IBM有
right okay so didn't you this so perfect
好的，那么你不是那么完美吗
um now we have everything set up so
嗯，现在我们已经设置好一切
what's impressed and interesting for me
给我留下深刻印象和有趣的是
is no super poems no plugins everything
没有超级诗歌没有插件一切
forbidden so this is like this is the
禁止的，所以这就是
the the blueprint for a Java 8 project
Java 8项目的蓝图
so if if now the profile is will come
所以如果现在有个人资料
and I will have you know to open the
我会让你知道打开
micro profile and you will see that 200
微型个人资料，您会看到200
dependencies to micro profile and 300
微观档案和300的依存关系
Java EE eight profile this I'm
我是Java EE八个配置文件
absolutely not interested in it why not
对此完全不感兴趣，为什么不
because it's not maintainable not simple
因为它不可维护并不简单
and this is not Java so do something
这不是Java，所以要做些什么
else but this is the philosophy is
否则，这就是哲学
completely different
完全不同
agreed so what you should at least agree
同意，所以你至少应该同意
this is simpler than the exploded format
这比爆炸格式更简单
how it's called best-of-breed we're a
它被称为“同类最佳”
bit before the pond project you have
在池塘项目之前
investigation phase you know which
调查阶段，您知道哪个
version of a login framework should I
版本的登录框架应该
choose and which version of jax-rs
选择和jax-rs版本
implementation should I choose and then
我应该选择实施，然后
after the exploration phase the project
在探索阶段之后，项目
is usually over okay so now we can run
通常是可以的，所以现在我们可以运行
it and I would run it on payara why
它，我会在payara上运行它，为什么
because I use it right now in production
因为我现在在生产中使用它
and where is it fire of five should
五火应该在哪里
remember and white flight 14 is the only
记住，只有白色的第14班机
application server which doesn't support
不支持的应用服务器
all of the micro profile specs but they
所有的微轮廓规格，但它们
are doing better and better and they
越来越好，他们
have config and open tracing with the
具有配置并打开跟踪
Eggar
艾加
but they will support in the next
但他们会在接下来的支持
version more and more payara supports
版本越来越多的payara支持
200 full open Liberty supports
200个完全开放的Liberty支持
everything and Tommy supports all my
一切，汤米全力支持我
micro profile but not everything for
微型个人资料，但并非所有
Java eight right
Java八对
not quite so what is there prolongs
不完全是，所以延长了
Tommy
汤米
okay so Tommy is supporting towards
好吧，汤米正在支持
everything so by the way what you saw
一切顺便说一句
right now was complete reboot of
现在已经完全重启
everything here this is like the cloudy
这里的一切就像多云
started and we have enjoyed Java 8 so
开始，我们喜欢Java 8，所以
now what's interesting me is of course
现在我当然很有趣
what's going on here
这里发生了什么
Jake on and the only thing which matters
杰克和唯一重要的事情
for me is that and you see that Jake on
对我来说就是，你看到杰克在
war is three and a half K why it's the
战争是三个半K为什么它是
case because yeah I don't have to deploy
案例，因为是的，我不必部署
to ship my application infrastructure
运送我的应用程序基础架构
again and this is why I'm still doing
再次，这就是为什么我仍然在做
Java EE and even more and more in cloud
Java EE以及越来越多的云计算
native environment because the pushes
本机环境，因为推动
are fast so to demonstrate you this I
很快，所以向你展示一下我
would like to just create a docker
只想创建一个码头工人
deployment which is just to give you an
部署只是为了给您一个
feeling and I think it comes with
感觉，我认为它带有
GlassFish and I wanted to use PI R 5 PI
GlassFish和我想使用PI R 5 PI
R 5 so what it means is it just uses it
R 5所以它意味着用它
uses the payara 5 as a base image and
使用payara 5作为基本图片，
and now I do a full build clean cleaner
现在我做一个完整的清洁工
it doesn't exist
它不存在
install and talk build - T
安装和交谈构建-T
let's call it Jacon Jacon
我们称之为Jacon Jacon
no jaqen one right so this is his
没有jaqen一个权利，所以这是他的
t-shirt so we have that and hopefully it
T恤，所以我们有，希望它
would build no now we have full built
不会建立，现在我们已经完整建立
and the docker image is created so this
并创建了docker映像，因此
is the docker image comprises of payara
是docker图片包含的payara
fool it's the largest available
傻瓜这是最大的
applications ever out there I would say
我会说那里的应用程序
payara I never used a smaller payara
我从未使用过较小的payara
because it doesn't matter it uses sent
因为它使用发送都没关系
OS 7 the largest known not alpine Linux
OS 7最大的已知非高山Linux
and open JDK also full without any
并打开JDK也完全没有任何
tricks so this diverse possible
技巧，所以这种多样的可能
experience you can get and behind the
您可以得到和获得的经验
scenes a cloud is also running on a
场景也正在云上运行
machine so it cannot be slower than this
机器，所以它不能比这慢
and if this slower usually one project
如果这个比较慢的项目通常
everything escalated and it turn out
一切都升级了，事实证明
then they are runing running virus
然后他们正在运行正在运行的病毒
scanner and the virus scanner scans the
扫描程序和病毒扫描程序扫描
JVM itself so it was the securest
JVM本身，因此它是最安全的
deployment ever so now doc doc I run - D
部署，所以现在运行doc doc-D
- P I have to be careful with the port H
-PI必须注意端口H
- H - H - 8080 and this also no one does
-H-H-8080这也没人做
that in production what I usually use is
在生产中我通常使用的是
openshift and openshift integrates
openshift和openshift集成
kubernetes h a proxy etcd
kubernetes ha代理etcd
in the whole deployment but this is what
在整个部署中，但这就是
you could start with docker run - D -
您可以从docker run开始-D-
Peters and then we call that name is one
彼得斯，然后我们称之为那个名字
and the name was Jake on one hopefully
希望这个名字叫杰克
yes dr. PS is running dr. Luke's one is
是的，博士PS正在运行博士。路加的是
running and and now Doka history one
运行，现在多卡历史之一
[Music]
[音乐]
yeah darker history jaqen one
是的，历史越深，jaqen一
so now we're all young developers so
所以现在我们都是年轻的开发者
Java's
Java的
the most young fresh language so what do
最年轻的新鲜语言，怎么办
we have here you see two years ago I
我们在这里，你看到两年前我
installed probably sent to a seven I
安装大概送给我七
guess nineteen years nineteen years
猜十九年十九年
nineteen months ago it was I guess open
十九个月前我猜是开放的
JDK or something and what what's
JDK之类的东西是什么
interesting is the upper the stack so
有趣的是堆栈的上方，所以
fresh it is so this was probably payara
新鲜，所以这可能是payara
5 this is 5 month months old payara
5这是5个月大的payara
and what I did one minute ago I I
一分钟前我做了什么
created and docker image which is 4k big
创建和4k大的docker映像
so and after this demonstration
在这个示范之后
everyone loves actually Java why because
每个人实际上都喜欢Java，原因是
you push the whole image to the private
您将整个形象推向私人
registry of your cloud and then you push
您的云注册表，然后您推送
you know 2,000 times a day 4k so having
你一天4k知道2,000次，所以
that said none of my production image is
说我的生产形象都不是
4k but usually most of them are smaller
4k，但通常大多数都较小
than one Mac and our podcast will come
一台Mac，我们的播客就会来
out soon how big were your images I
很快，您的图片有多大
forgot it because you have the whole how
忘记了，因为你拥有整个
was called not the cloud stuff from IBM
被称为不是IBM的云技术
the host not hudson what's the name of
主人不是哈德森，哈瓦那叫什么名字
the guy
那家伙
no Jenkins not Hudson the Watson
没有詹金斯，没有沃森的哈德森
yeah he has a parts of Watson in the war
是的，他在战争中拥有沃森的一部分
and it still small enough how how big
它仍然足够小
was it five max or something five max
是五个最大还是五个最大
because of what's an API is but what
因为什么是API，但是什么
soon is okay is not a part of Java so
很快就可以了，不是Java的一部分，所以
you have to package Watson questions
你必须打包沃森问题
about that so I can tell you this is
关于这个，所以我可以告诉你这是
what I do
我所做的
after the show so did all the time this
演出后一直如此
okay no feed link with dependencies and
好的，没有具有依赖项的供稿链接，并且
the question is or the question I don't
问题是还是我没有
care how big the platform is because the
关心平台有多大，因为
platform is never deployed to the cloud
平台永远不会部署到云
now you can say how big is the image
现在你可以说图像有多大
then and this is what I can show you
然后这就是我可以告诉你的
so and the image here is you see 500 mix
所以，这里的图像是您看到500混合
FiberNet these are lots of images so and
FiberNet这些映像很多，因此
so this is the last one it's 583 minutes
这是最后一个583分钟
ago 70 hours is something it and yeah
70个小时以前是这样，是的
elasticsearch and whatever but they're
elasticsearch以及其他任何东西
around 560 max so of course impossible
最大约560，所以当然不可能
to have that large hard disk for all the
有那么大的硬盘
images but what daca does is of course
图像，但daca所做的当然是
pi RS once on my machine and all other
pi RS一次在我的机器上
images refer to the same just like you
图像就像你一样指代相同
know consistent hashing omega-3 okay
知道一致的哈希Omega-3好吗
so and the funny story is I did some
所以有趣的故事是我做了一些
service Java and the function image was
服务Java，功能映像为
larger than the application server just
比应用服务器大
one function right okay this lightweight
一个功能好吗，这个轻量级
okay take a look at the size and it was
好吧，看看它的大小
larger and my project next week with the
更大，下周我的项目
open Liberty properly we all have to use
正确开放自由，我们所有人都必须使用
lambda functions because of marketing
lambda由于营销而起作用
and what what we what we will do
以及我们将做什么
probably because of our activity package
可能是因为我们的活动套餐
open Liberty has a lambda function
开放自由具有lambda函数
because it's more productive and this is
因为它更有生产力，这是
small enough it doesn't matter whether
足够小是否重要
it is you know 500 mix or 520 in the one
你知道500个混合料还是520个混合料
case about this so I'm just just to give
关于这个案例，所以我只是给
you impression so before you justify
你的印象，所以在你辩解之前
what is lightweight or heavyweight just
什么是轻量级或重量级的
measure and see how it behaves this is
测量并查看其行为
my advice you will be surprised you know
我的建议你会惊讶的知道
how it really looks in in in in
它的实际外观
production any questions yeah
生产任何问题是的
not conference I'm not the confessor I
不是会议我不是not悔者
try to avoid conferences just an hacking
尽量避免会议只是黑客
project no conference no she asked me
项目没有会议没有她问我
give give me clients and no I cannot I
给我客户，不，我不能
have NDA's everywhere you know this is
到处都有NDA，你知道这是
the problem if you have consultant there
问题，如果你在那里有顾问
first you have to sign paper like you
首先，你必须像你一样签纸
cannot tell anyone you're doing Java
无法告诉任何人您正在使用Java
yeah so now we have the basis now what
是的，所以现在我们有了依据
about micro profile now how much time do
关于微轮廓现在多少时间
we have
我们有
Marcus how much time where is the guy
马库斯这家伙多少时间在哪里
with the fancy 15 minutes very good so
花哨的15分钟非常好
what happened so far nothing so this was
到目前为止发生了什么事，所以这是
Java 8 with one single endpoint and
Java 8具有一个单一端点，并且
usually what you would like to have is
通常你想要的是
you will have to have a kind of facade
你将不得不有一种立面
and I would like to call it pink let's
我想称它为粉红色
say it's service and I will create a
说这是服务，我将创建一个
mess here because it doesn't matter
乱七八糟，因为没关系
it's a session after the session there's
这是一个会议之后的会议
up how to structure this so I can clean
弄清楚这个的结构以便我可以清洁
up the mess right so and now are usually
所以现在通常都是一团糟
you will would like to have stage
你想有个舞台
independent configuration and how it
独立配置以及如何配置
works in cloud native you will have to
在本机云中工作，您将不得不
look up their stuff in environment
在环境中查找他们的东西
entries and then in system properties
条目，然后在系统属性中
usually or whatever source you have so
通常或您拥有的任何来源
in Java you cannot do this usually a
在Java中，您通常无法执行此操作
hack on stage the Java away which is
在舞台上砍掉Java，这是
like one-liner I deleted the one-liner
就像单线一样，我删除了单线
because there is an even better stuff
因为有更好的东西
called conflict property and there's two
叫做冲突财产，有两个
name just you can use the name which is
命名就可以使用
the name of the property call it message
属性的名称将其称为消息
and then you have the default value and
然后您具有默认值和
call it Jake on one Jake on one and then
称它为杰克（Jake on a）杰克（Jake）
say here at inject
在注入说
and then string message and this is
然后是字符串消息，这是
configured and this is configured with
已配置，并且已配置
default it goes to environment entries
默认情况下它进入环境条目
and then it goes in system properties
然后进入系统属性
and if you not satisfied with that you
如果您不满意您
can provide your own config sources with
可以提供您自己的配置源
priorities I never did that but this is
我从来没有做过的优先事项，但这是
no it is possible to do this for
不，有可能这样做
instance Microsoft Asia did it
实例Microsoft Asia做到了
they have config sources for Microsoft
他们有微软的配置源
Asia they come out of the box provided
他们提供了开箱即用的亚洲
by Microsoft why that because Microsoft
微软为什么会这样，因为微软
is a part of Jakarta II and why that
是雅加达II的一部分，为什么
because Bruno Burgess evangelist at
因为Bruno Burgess的传教士
Oracle now works with Microsoft right so
Oracle现在可以与Microsoft合作，因此
and this is like the short cycle so now
这就像一个短周期，所以现在
we have this and let's say I would like
我们有这个，说我想
to have here thank good morning and what
在这里感谢早上好，还有什么
all projects to because it's easy now we
所有项目，因为现在很容易
have graph Anna and the other graph Anna
有图安娜和另一个图安娜
and the other keep on a graph Anna and
另一个继续做图Anna和
or other Ivana's and a problem is no
或其他伊凡娜的，问题不是
kidding last year a client came to me
去年在开玩笑，一位客户来找我
and say we have lots of dashboards but
说我们有很多仪表板，但是
we cannot tell whether our use case is
我们无法确定我们的用例是否
successful so I was really curious about
成功的，所以我真的很好奇
the dashboards and I look at the
仪表板，我看着
dashboards and they could tell you
仪表板，他们可以告诉你
everything probably even no temperature
一切都可能没有温度
in the room and size of the I don't know
在房间和大小我不知道
atoms inside the CPU but no one could
CPU内部的原子，但没人能
tell actually whether something was
告诉别人是否真的
bought or not so I'd look I have no idea
买或不买，所以我看起来我不知道
what you are building but for me your
你在建造什么，但对我来说
system is like a black box something
系统就像黑匣子一样
goes in and something goes out I would
进去，有些东西熄灭，我会
start with counting debt and they talked
从计算债务开始，他们开始谈论
and talked let's say you are genius now
并说了你现在是天才
only you with you know 20 years of
只有你和你一起知道20年的
experience can do something like this
经验可以做这样的事情
and what they could tell me you know how
他们会告诉我你知道如何
often the garbage collector ran like
垃圾收集器经常像
this is too often like I don't know and
这常常像我不知道，
I don't care if it works if you sell
我不在乎如果您出售它是否有效
your stuff let it run I mean if it's
你的东西让它运行我的意思是，如果
fast enough the garbage collector should
垃圾收集器应该足够快
also do something right so good morning
早上也做对的事
so then what you should start with for
所以那么你应该开始
instance you could do something like
实例你可以做类似的事情
this you can say I have a long Atta
这可以说我有很长的阿塔
it's a morning counter and the morning
这是一个早上柜台，早上
counter let's do it make it clear in
计数器让我们做清楚
post construct
后期构造
new equals yeah there's probably one
新等于是，大概有一个
language is more concise because there
语言更简洁，因为那里
is no equals so you can though there is
不等于，所以尽管有
we have this and then this morning
我们有这个，然后今天早上
counter increment and say return good
计数器增加并说返回良好
morning
早上
plus this message
加上这则讯息
so and now now the cool story is what we
所以现在，最酷的故事就是我们
start with why are we like micro profit
首先我们为什么喜欢微利
is the following we have end
以下是我们的结局
good-morning count and in this
早上好，在此
particular project would item sold so
特定项目会出售项目，因此
easy and they say okay but we promise
很简单，他们说还可以，但我们保证
use and the stuff again and do this
再次使用和东西，并执行此操作
gauge which is like counter and and then
像计数器然后然后
you have to specify units and this is a
您必须指定单位，这是一个
little bit strange so this could be
有点奇怪，所以这可能是
improved but we have time so there's
有所改善，但我们有时间，所以
four releases a year so we can
一年发行四个版本，因此我们可以
contribute and this is like let's say
做出贡献，就像说
either I say count or morning it doesn't
我说算数还是早上不算
matter this is that label in Prometheus
这是普罗米修斯的那个标签
later and what I have to do is to say
以后，我要做的就是说
return this where was the counter in
返回此计数器在哪里
value so and what this means is we have
因此很有价值，这意味着我们拥有
a monotonic monolithic monotonic counter
单调的整体式单调计数器
which just increases the values it is
只是增加了它的价值
named and we will see Prometheus in the
命名，我们将在其中看到普罗米修斯
dashboards how many how often good
仪表板多少好多少
morning was actually executed so this
早上实际上已经执行了，所以这
the only business logic I have it is
我唯一拥有的业务逻辑是
most interesting one and I do not care
最有趣的一个，我不在乎
about number of transactions number of
关于交易数
rollbacks this could be interesting in
回滚，这可能很有趣
debugging phase so the same if you buy a
调试阶段，如果您购买
car it is the most important thing is
车最重要的是
you know is it philip and does it does
你知道这是菲利普吗？
it go yeah i would like to see the speed
是的，我想看看速度
or i have to see the speed otherwise I
否则我必须看看速度，否则我
won't run a lot in Germany so and and if
如果在德国不会有很多经营
developers were car designers we would
开发人员是我们的汽车设计师
see you know in the dashboard like you
在仪表板中看到您知道的样子
know the temperature of the in Denver
知道丹佛市的温度
kicks of the engine or you know the
引擎的踢动，或者你知道
pressure in the exhaust pipes but no one
排气管中的压力，但没有人
will know whether we are actually
会知道我们是否真的
driving or not this is what what I see
开车还是不开车，这就是我所看到的
in projects right so gauge the most
在正确的项目中，因此最能衡量
important annotation so but you you know
重要的注释，所以你知道
I know you are developer so you can
我知道您是开发人员，因此您可以
start with meters for instance
以米开始
so what meter does you have the rolling
那你滚动什么米
average and the and
平均和
and the threshold and so forth and one
和阈值等等，还有一个
consultant told me he always starts with
顾问告诉我，他总是从
metered because then it looks more
计量，因为这样看起来更
professional so okay then I go with that
专业所以好吧那我就去
and and then afterwards you should and
然后，您应该然后
one point of time just start with simple
一个时间点只是从简单开始
but this is just a counter right so um
但这只是一个柜台吧
Oh Java user group in Hamburg actually
哦，汉堡的Java用户组
and so now we can just inject this and
所以现在我们可以注入这个
of course what now happens in my project
当然，现在我的项目中发生了什么
it's like to say you are crazy
就像说你疯了
you cannot go without private so okay if
你不能没有私人，所以如果
you really like I can do it private but
你真的很喜欢我可以私下做
it does not matter in Java you know one
在Java中没关系，您知道一个
will is able to access this directly so
将能够直接访问它，所以
if you like privates write it but it is
如果您喜欢私人写的话，那是
a waste of time now and what happens
现在浪费时间，发生什么事
then you know also now source of all
那么你现在也知道所有来源
Jenkins are just no Jenkins the sona
詹金斯只是没有詹娜斯的呐喊
source system blows up
源系统爆炸
oh very poor code quality there is one
哦，代码质量很差，只有一个
private like ink so now service good
私人喜欢墨水，所以现在服务很好
morning code review last week they
他们上周早上的代码回顾
tested default constructors of all data
测试所有数据的默认构造函数
transfer object and wrote a small
转移对象并写了一个小
introspection free bug which invokes all
无内省的错误，可调用所有
getters and setters also nice nice way
getters和setters也不错
to spend time so we have this hopefully
花时间，所以我们有希望
what a second it could even work I
它甚至可以工作一秒钟
forgot what's actually running so
忘记了实际正在运行的内容
this No
这个没有
should be different output and joy Joey
应该是不同的输出和喜悦乔伊
so let's run it again
让我们再次运行它
and if not I will run it on Daka
如果没有，我将在Daka上运行它
can you understand us
你能了解我们吗
I can
我可以
I read exactly
我看得很清楚
I ran maven clean install from command
我从命令运行了maven clean install
line which undeployed the whole
整个部署线
application so now I should see
应用程序，所以现在我应该看到
something think Jake on one and with ya
有些人认为杰克和一个人在一起
and now with matrix data these are the
现在有了矩阵数据
matrix if you would like to look
矩阵，如果你想看
professional so you will see everything
专业，所以您会看到的一切
right and what what's cool
对了，什么是酷
[Music]
[音乐]
they're available as Jason so it is
他们有Jason的名字，所以
really easy to build a simple web app
构建简单的Web应用程序真的很容易
and expose them without prometheus for
并在没有普罗米修斯的情况下暴露他们
instance but even cooler now what's
实例，但现在更酷了
really interesting is the scope
真正有趣的是范围
application so and now you see my
应用程序，现在您看到我的
business matrix and these are the bags
业务矩阵，这些就是袋子
so you can build the dashboard and see
这样您就可以构建仪表板并查看
you know how many items are sold or how
你知道售出多少物品或如何
many frauds were actually attempted so I
实际上有很多欺诈行为，所以我
have to admit I misuse Prometheus for
必须承认我误用了普罗米修斯
business matrix and graph on ax all the
业务矩阵和轴上的所有图
time so my dashboards are not that
时间，所以我的仪表盘不是
exciting but my clients really like that
令人兴奋，但我的客户真的很喜欢
okay now even further right so the next
好吧，现在就更远了，所以下一个
question is yeah but we need hystrix
问题是，但是我们需要hystrix
okay if you like do it but what we could
好的，如果您愿意，但是我们可以
do actually yeah and by the way this
确实是的，顺便说一句
works
作品
accidentally
偶然
this would be better application scoped
这将是更好的应用范围
now what we could do we can say this
现在我们可以做什么，我们可以这样说
good morning is a really slow operation
早上好，手术真的很慢
and it could also throw arrows so what I
它也可能会抛出箭头，所以我
could do is I could apply the circuit
可以做的是我可以应用电路
breaker for instance sir quit breaker is
断路器，例如，先生退出断路器是
building without unfortunately without
建筑物没有不幸的是没有
history and so um so your wall was still
历史等等，所以你的墙还在
small in the one project that they
在一个项目中他们很小
deployed histories in the whole
全面部署历史
infrastructure with the with the Java EE
Java EE与基础架构
so that everything twice everything with
这样，一切都会变成两倍
Java applications have I can provide
我可以提供的Java应用程序
plus histories now circuit breaker so we
现在加上历史的断路器，所以我们
can say for instance request volume
可以说例如请求量
threshold 10 failure ratio is 1/2 and
门槛10失败率是1/2，
and success is 2 so what this means is
成功是2，所以这意味着
if 5 out of 10 requests are will fail
如果10个请求中有5个失败
their secret breaker will open and and
他们的秘密断路器将打开，并且
after two of the timeout period which is
在两个超时时间之后
usually I think five seconds the success
通常我认为成功五秒钟
threshold of two and it will close again
门槛为2，它将再次关闭
so this is circle breaker and if you can
所以这是破环者，如果可以的话
say okay but I need a fallback and the
说好的，但是我需要一个备用广告，
fallback is fallback method is default
fallback是默认的fallback方法
morning so
所以早上
they have to correspond and I can say
他们必须对应，我可以说
return still nice so and now what
返回仍然很好，现在又是什么
happens is on error we don't have any
发生错误是我们没有任何错误
arrows but we can introduce some
箭头，但我们可以介绍一些
so
所以
so now
所以现在
should still work where is it
应该在哪里工作
it's too nice so we have this what we
太好了，所以我们有了这个
else interesting probably are what I did
其他有趣的事情可能就是我所做的
a little bit differently Java 8 I use
我使用的Java 8有点不同
managed executor service and use the
托管执行人服务并使用
jax-rs and the complete every future
jax-rs和完整的每一个未来
pipeline to implement bulkheads there
在那里实施舱壁的管道
are even nicer now I can say I would
现在更好了，我可以说我会
just comment it out I could say hey
只是说出来我可以说嘿
these are buckets
这些是水桶
and the bucket is no bulkheads
铲斗没有隔板
and I have specify a value of two but
我指定了两个值
this is strange why that value and
这很奇怪，为什么这个价值和
waiting task you exactly so we have a
您正等待任务，所以我们有一个
value of two but the interesting part is
值两个，但有趣的是
the waiting task of let's say one and
让我们说一个等待的任务
then I will delete that again and what
那么我将再次删除该内容
does means is now only one thread at a
确实意味着现在只有一个线程
time can access the method and if if the
时间可以访问该方法，如果
queue fits up here then the fallback is
队列适合这里，那么回退是
going to be called so as actually very
被称为实际上
easy to understand what happens behind
容易理解背后发生的事情
the scenes if you need it so I'm a
如果您需要的话，我是一个
really bit afraid this is they also
真的有点害怕，这也是他们
started with all the patterns then they
从所有模式开始，然后他们
first they will you know introduce all
首先他们会知道介绍所有吗
the annotations all the patterns and
注释所有模式和
then afterwards they way we think about
然后他们以他们的方式思考
what they actually would like to build
他们实际上想要建立什么
but I think you should start at the
但我认为您应该从
beginning to break your applications
开始破坏您的应用程序
using stress tests and if the
使用压力测试，如果
application breaks it's a really nice
应用程序中断，这真的很不错
thing to do to fix that with building
用建筑来解决这个问题
annotations so we have packet of two and
注释，所以我们有两个包
I will make the application a little bit
我将使该应用程序有点
slower thread sleep
较慢的线程睡眠
and let's say no longer one second
再说一秒钟
now let's see if I'm lucky so it should
现在让我们看看我是否很幸运，应该
mean if I'm fast and one point of time I
意思是如果我快又有一点时间
should only see default morning until
应该只看到默认的早晨，直到
the DQ becomes empty so now try that
DQ变成空的，所以现在尝试
too fast even for Joey
连乔伊都太快了
no it's okay you just
不，你还好
no it's okay Lucy it waits for a second
不，还好，露西，它等待一秒钟
it waits and then if I'm too fast till
它会等待，然后如果我太快直到
nice fall back then I wait a little bit
很好的回落，然后我稍等
it works so this is the indicator if I'm
它有效，所以这是指标，如果我
too fast it falls back okay understood
太快了，它会退回
bulkhead built-in now the night story is
内置舱壁现在的夜晚故事是
may even clean install now my
甚至可以干净安装我的
application grows because history rings
应用程序的增长是因为历史敲响了
and everything is inside so now we have
一切都在里面，所以现在我们有了
5k of course it doesn't looks
5k当然看起来
professional so what you can do it can
专业，所以你可以做的可以
create you know some heavy jars without
创建你知道一些没有
any implementation just to look more
任何实现只是为了看起来更多
professional but it's not required right
专业，但这不是必需的
so um now this is my daily work with
所以现在这是我每天的工作
Java this is actually what I do and not
Java这实际上是我要做的，而不是
only eyes on actually startups are using
只关注实际的初创企业
this more and more because it's that
这越来越多，因为那是
productive by the way what you usually
像平时一样高效
also do we never play directly with
我们也不要直接玩吗
OpenShift mini shift console how much
OpenShift mini移位控制台多少钱
time do you have
你有时间
Marko's yeah you're only on Facebook the
Marko是的，您只在Facebook上
whole time okay
一直都可以
so doesn't run on my proof concept but
所以不是基于我的证明概念
this is running Venice scenes and this
这是威尼斯的场景，这
is this is white flight 14 running on
这是白色的航班14
Cuban it is hae TCD and so forth
古巴是TCD等
proof concept called micro Java he has
他拥有的称为微型Java的证明概念
nothing to do with the conference but I
与会议无关，但我
thought I could show you how it behaves
以为我可以告诉你它的表现
in the clouds and so what I could do to
在云中，所以我能做些什么
show you let's go with the micro
告诉你让我们一起去吧
okay now I'm micro so I would like to
好吧，我现在是微，所以我想
start the build I do a full push with
开始构建，我全力以赴
kubernetes right now micro and the war
Kubernetes现在微与战争
is also micro and now so
也是微的，现在如此
what's that
那是什么
so this was killed and the other one is
所以这被杀死了，另一个是
started done so and this is actually
开始这样做，这实际上是
this was slow this is very first time
这很慢，这是第一次
today so I do it again this was full
今天我再做一次
deployment of a Java iPod on white fly
飞上部署Java iPod
fool so it is not it is not micro for
傻瓜，不是，不是，因为不是
profit capable but I'll show you this
有利润，但我会告诉你
again
再次
where was it
在哪
yeah
是的
so do it again and watch this
所以再做一次，看这个
and SS this is usually how it works if
和SS这通常是如何工作的，如果
it is slower than this usually have a
它比这通常有一个慢
bandwidth problem between the registry
注册表之间的带宽问题
or the dock or whatever and this was
或码头之类的东西
binary built so what it means is indeed
二进制构建的，所以它的意思确实是
and it pulls the sent to i7 was white
它拉到发送到i7是白色
from the docker registry and I'm just
从泊坞窗注册表中，我只是
replacing their war this is this
取代他们的战争，这是这个
actually clouds and similarly well it
实际上是乌云密布的
works in ECS Amazon ECS one of project
在ECS中工作Amazon ECS项目之一
we use ECS from Amazon so actually and
我们使用亚马逊的ECS，因此实际上和
there was never the case were we found
从来没有发现我们
the application server too large why
应用服务器太大
because usually it's always the same
因为通常总是一样
size 500 Meg's and what what what what's
500 Meg的大小，什么是什么
inside Java comes with about 150
Java内置约150个
megabyte or more installed on your hard
硬盘上已安装了兆字节或更多
disk open JDK sent where seven comes to
磁盘打开JDK发送到七个
around 200 mix and most of the
大约200种混合物，大部分
application servers are around 200 makes
应用服务器大约有200个
on the hard disk the open Liberty is the
在硬盘上，打开的Liberty是
smallest but it's not like you know it
最小，但不像您知道的那样
is five mix and the GlassFish has 200
是五个混合，GlassFish有200个
miss or two geeks they are very very
小姐或两个极客，他们非常非常
similar okay questions yes
类似的好问题是
yes
是
but they are default this is what I show
但它们是默认值，这就是我所展示的
is lesser-known what you can do you can
鲜为人知的是你能做什么
start build and I will have to point to
开始构建，我将不得不指出
our to our github registry and tell you
我们到我们的github注册表，告诉你
just work so this is actually easier to
只是工作，所以实际上更容易
show you an STI built if there are no
告诉你如果没有的话建立的STI
other questions I will show you this so
其他问题我会给你看
I I will have to go here to whitefly and
我将不得不去这里粉虱和
this is 14 application name pink and I
这是14个应用程序名称pink，我
need a repository now go here and I'm
现在需要一个存储库，我在这里
being pink any other questions this
变粉红色还有其他问题吗
doesn't matter this is just fun
没关系，这很有趣
yeah what's wrong with you you can say
是的，你怎么了，你可以说
this was too complicated we don't like
这太复杂了，我们不喜欢
it everything is crazy
一切都疯了
we need to rust to be efficient or
我们需要生锈以提高效率或
whatever right so with a little bit of
随便吧
luck so now this ping is started this
运气好，现在开始这个ping
isn't complete s2 i image unprepared
不完整的s2我未准备好映像
which pulls from from dhaka everything
从dhaka提取一切
so now the Maven build is started
所以现在开始Maven构建
whether it works on though I don't know
它是否有效，尽管我不知道
I just tried that let's see what happens
我只是试着让我们看看会发生什么
so this is a full build with without it
所以这是没有它的完整版本
is already pushed so it was already
已经被推，所以它已经
built from and pushed it means we have
建立并推动它意味着我们拥有
now deployment and pink this was the
现在部署和粉红色这是
pink and let's take a look it's already
粉红色，让我们看一下它已经
started so unfortunately is also quick
开始如此不幸也很快
so what I will have to do is to say OC
所以我要做的就是说OC
expose service pink now I get and public
我现在公开并公开服务粉色
route routable address services pink
路由可路由地址服务粉红色
yeah and this is the white fly pink
是的，这是粉红色的白色
resources I think no just pink right
我认为资源不只是粉红色而已
yeah this is my project from github and
是的，这是我来自github的项目，
now it this was the full deployment from
现在，这是从
github with image which comes with open
带有打开的图像的github
shift I have no idea what happened but
转变我不知道发生了什么
this was the pure s2i image what I
这是纯s2i图像，我
usually use the binary s2i image so you
通常使用二进制s2i映像，因此您
can push wars' directly without
可以直接推动战争而无需
rebuilding that
重建那个
okay any other questions criticism
好的，还有其他问题吗？
whatever so and this now we have in
无论如何，现在我们有了
micro profile we get concurrency API
微观配置文件，我们获得并发API
which is also nicely wave complete
这也很好波完成
control over concurrency which could be
控制并发
interestingly building your own batch
有趣地建立自己的批处理
jobs and more control over you know the
工作和对您的更多控制权
concurrency but I have to say I'm really
并发，但我必须说我真的
pleased with micro profile and by the
对微轮廓感到满意，并受到
way what I forgot
我忘了的方式
dddd coolest stuff is because I cannot
dddd最酷的东西是因为我不能
see it anymore in project is 8080 open
在项目中看到它了8080已打开
API so you get a default swagger or open
API，因此您可以默认打开或打开
API endpoint without any annotations and
API端点，无任何注释，并且
if you get the annotations the
如果您获得注释
annotations come with micro profile so
注释附带了微型配置文件，因此
and so it means what I see is the
所以这意味着我看到的是
complete swagger pollution so everything
彻底的招摇污染，所以一切
has swagger runtime is swagger
大摇大摆的运行时
annotations and the best thing is the
注释，最好的是
output from swagger you will see now get
昂首阔步的输出，您现在将看到
customers and the end the documentation
客户和最终文档
is the best like get customers returns
是最好的获得客户回报的方式
customers if they are good yeah if they
客户，如果他们很好，是的，如果他们
are lazy get customers or delete
懒惰获取客户或删除
customers they delete customer yeah or
客户，他们删除客户yeah或
if this is not research resource
如果这不是研究资源
oriented like remote procedure call rest
面向远程过程调用休息
does this get customer detail that says
这是否获得客户详细信息，说明
invokes method get customer details oh I
调用方法获取客户详细信息哦，我
have to say swagger is as bad as no soap
不得不说招摇不如没有肥皂一样糟糕
was before and VHDL was the same the
之前和VHDL是相同的
idea was good but the execution is
想法很好，但执行力是
terrible at least in enterprise projects
至少在企业项目中很糟糕
okay
好的
redlight or you wanted to show me
红灯或您想让我看看
something
某事
oh I'm already time out certain
哦，我已经超时了
questions
问题
other questions we can ask a link where
其他问题，我们可以问一个链接
a seconds I will try a scale to think Oh
一秒钟我会尝试一个秤来思考哦
C scale DC pink replicas equals 2
C刻度DC粉红副本等于2
scaled where is it
在哪里缩放
we have to see this
我们必须看到这个
no micro Java
没有微型Java
we have what we have here two parts of
我们在这里有两个部分
the thing - now we can go with three
事情-现在我们可以三个
and now this is the project which I
现在这是我的项目
downloaded from github now we have three
从github下载，现在我们有三个
with full whitefly I get the question
满满的粉虱我明白了
why are not using how it's called white
为什么不使用它的白色
fries warm or thorn tail and my answer
炸薯条温暖或刺尾，我的答案
is do you think it's going to be faster
你认为它会更快吗
than this
比这个
if yes I would use it if not I don't
如果是的话，我会使用它，如果不是，我不会
care okay
好吧
now we have three instances behind load
现在我们有三个实例落后
balancer with Java EE plus micro profile
Java EE加微型配置文件的平衡器
full stack diverse possible experience
全栈多样的可能体验
you can get and the this is just oldest
你可以得到，这是最古老的
make book available with this design
通过该设计制作书籍
this is the truth
这是事实
any other questions if not after the
如果没有其他任何问题
session I will show you how to build
会议上，我将向您展示如何构建
reasonable apps how to structure them
合理的应用程序如何构建它们
with job' so could be fun
工作”可能会很有趣
I'm staying here so I'm no questions
我待在这里所以我没有问题
yeah
是的
yeah your talk is when
是的，你的谈话是什么时候
one for 15 to 5
一到十五到五
Emily will talk about micro profile and
艾米丽（Emily）将谈论微观概况和
you should really attend because she
你真的应该参加，因为她
knows about a micro profile really I'm
我知道我的个人资料
just a user so I'm using the stuff and
只是一个用户，所以我正在使用这些东西，
she's designing so if you're not happy
她在设计，如果你不开心
what you saw today go to her and say
你今天看到的去找她说
okay you have to change that you know
好吧，你必须改变你知道的
this is to complicate it or whatever
这会使它复杂化
right really so you have to attend the
真的，所以你必须参加
session to be as you're also talking
会话就像你在说话一样
here Oh
在这里哦
vacations any other question was wrong
休假还有其他任何问题吗
never if I knew this next time I will
如果我下次再也不会知道
just take up keynote I thought I will be
只是做主题演讲，我想我会
no more human some slides and it worked
没有更多的人一些幻灯片，它的工作
South after using micro profile what's
南使用微轮廓后是什么
your like a feedback and which areas
您喜欢反馈以及哪些领域
need to be improved and so on which
需要改进等等
areas you think work well so what some
您认为有效的领域
there are small things like for instance
有一些小事情，例如
the health nurse checks so usually you
健康护士通常会检查您
get readiness and liveness checks so
得到准备和活力检查
they have to be separated in it's
他们必须分开
probably already solved my feedback was
可能已经解决了我的反馈意见是
so obvious that I thought I don't put it
很明显，我以为我不放
because you're already working on it
因为你已经在做
probably and and and this I have to say
可能和，而我不得不说
I really like that and this micro
我真的很喜欢这个
profile is our github project so you can
个人资料是我们的github项目，因此您可以
go to github and and and just help and
转到github和并且只是帮助和
pull requests and most of the people you
拉取请求和大多数人
already know the lots of Germans I saw
我已经知道很多德国人
from from Red Hat right so you can get a
来自Red Hat的权利，所以您可以获得
direct feedback and you do have a good
直接的反馈，你确实有一个很好的
idea you can start your own project Oh
想法你可以开始自己的项目哦
another killer feature of micro profiler
Micro Profiler的另一个杀手级功能
completely forgot to mention but there
完全忘了提，但是那里
was no way I could show you this in one
我不可能一成不变地向你展示
project we had to use a key claw yeah
我们必须使用钥匙爪的项目
kick log for opens open SSO and this was
踢日志打开SSO，这是
a payara project and then you have to
payara项目，然后您必须
use servlet adapters from from from key
从from键使用servlet适配器
clock which
时钟哪个
you will end up having additional
您最终将拥有更多
dependency which is big in stable and so
依赖性很大，因此稳定
forth and what we did this key clock is
来，我们做了这个关键的时钟是
off too and micro profiler comes with
也关闭了，Micro Profiler附带了
GWT jason web token so and what we did
GWT Jason Web令牌如此，我们做了什么
is we used a micro profile with JSON web
是我们在JSON网站上使用了微型配置文件
token without any dependencies to kick
没有任何依赖的标记
lock we want to have thin Wars and it
锁，我们想打一场战争，它
worked perfectly and this was and open
工作完美，这是开放的
liberty has even better support or
自由有更好的支持或
easier support the only thing was you
更容易的支持是你
know the only I would say challenge was
知道我唯一要说的挑战是
the sharing of the key but this like is
密钥的共享，但这是
this is like a cryptography so the
这就像一个密码，所以
public and private key have to be split
公钥和私钥必须分开
but for instance this another and what
但例如这又是什么
you get with micro profile you can
有了微轮廓，您可以
inject these JSON web token tokens or
注入这些JSON Web令牌令牌或
how would we call it the three parts
我们怎么称呼这三个部分
directly so you get the injection and
直接进行注射
the JWT user is automatically converted
JWT用户将自动转换
to principal and all the roles so it
担任校长和所有角色
works out of the box and this was as a
开箱即用，这是作为一个
my client was really delighted they say
我的客户很高兴他们说
this really cool because our web app not
这真的很酷，因为我们的网络应用程序不
angular because we are also know also
有角的，因为我们也知道
reasonable in the front-end so um our
在前端合理，所以我们
web app talks to key clock with single
Web应用程序与单键通话
sign-on and use the C JSON web token
登录并使用C JSON Web令牌
sentence back to PI era and we are
一句话可以追溯到PI时代，我们
authenticated and this was this was
经过身份验证，这是
actually great so this is an open API is
真的很棒，所以这是一个开放的API
also you can kill swag annotations which
你也可以杀死赃物注释
I really hate everyone dependency to
我真的很讨厌每个人的依赖
swagger then you get the JSON web token
大摇大摆，然后您将获得JSON Web令牌
and from Java EE
并且来自Java EE
aid I think the huge improvement is SL
帮助我认为巨大的进步是SL
375 I guess or 275 is the security API
我猜是375还是275是安全性API
so you get one injection point and you
所以你得到一个注射点，你
have yours all the users and all the
拥有您所有的用户和所有
roles in a hash map so basically you can
哈希图中的角色，因此基本上您可以
implement your own store it's very very
实现自己的商店，这非常非常
easy HTTP authentication built-in so for
内置简单的HTTP身份验证，因此
me it route it looks great and what my
我的路线看起来很棒，我的
only afraid of the optimization that the
只怕优化
community will start Java is too big we
社区将启动Java太大了
need 50 profiles and and now we need to
需要50个配置文件，现在我们需要
know better breed forget it so it is
知道更好的品种就算了吧
very small keep it like it is and I will
保持很小的样子，我会
call it the X developer experience and
称之为X开发人员体验，
what I would expect from Jakarta I that
我对雅加达的期望是
will say look from developer you have
会说您拥有的开发人员的外观
one dependency use it Mac I prefer the
一个依赖项使用它Mac我更喜欢
same you know one bomb use it not like
同样，你知道一个炸弹使用它不喜欢
every developer
每个开发人员
have to pull their own dependencies and
必须拉自己的依赖
the worst idea ever was the first
最糟糕的想法是第一个
edition of white fly swarm well you have
白色苍蝇群的版本，你有
to create there was like a maven wizard
创建那里就像一个maven向导
where you can put your dependencies and
您可以在其中放置依赖项
it created with a huge mechanism an
它创建了一个巨大的机制
application server with the application
应用服务器与应用程序
inside so what it means is if I build
里面的意思是如果我建立
the application once I would rebuild the
该应用程序一旦我将重建
whole runtime through the application
通过应用程序的整个运行时
and I say you are crazy and now they
我说你疯了，现在他们
introduced hollow jar way better
介绍中空罐子的方法更好
one application server never build it
一台应用服务器永远不会构建它
again and you're just building what
再一次，你只是在建造什么
changes ok and sure the contrast is it
改变确定并确定对比度
over or we have two hours to speak like
结束，或者我们有两个小时像
over yeah any questions
是的，任何问题
yeah questions so this list yeah at
是的，所以这个清单是
least one and not from speaker barcodes
至少一个，不是来自扬声器条形码
from you oh ok probably bad sign oh one
从你那里，好吧，可能是坏兆头
question they're two questions
问题是两个问题
do you have any experience with
你有什么经验吗
bring-bring boot so not a lot so you
带上靴子，所以不是很多，所以你
head in this was a funny story actually
其实这是一个有趣的故事
well last year they they hired me tis
好吧，去年他们雇用了我
was a spring boot project I didn't knew
是我不知道的 spring boot 项目
that and they thought this is Java EE
那，他们认为这是Java EE
and they found me and they called me and
他们找到了我，他们给我打电话，
they look at this like there's no Java
他们看起来像没有Java
so I mean why not because it's called
所以我的意思是为什么不，因为它被称为
spring boot okay now and I have no idea
spring boot 好吧，现在我不知道
about spring boot so what I did I create
关于 spring boot ，所以我做了什么
it all the proof of concept on white
这一切都是白色的概念证明
flight and they asked me why you are so
航班，他们问我为什么如此
fast right away so quick the deployment
立即快速，因此快速部署
I'm sorry I don't know usually people
对不起，我通常不认识别人
complain diploma it's slow like no it's
抱怨文凭慢，就像没有
incredibly fast and they showed me what
快得令人难以置信，他们告诉我了什么
they are doing it was like I didn't know
他们正在做那就像我不知道
that but one deployment on spring boot
那只是在 spring boot 上的一个部署
took like one minute and they end up
花了大约一分钟，他们最终
having in the jar everything you are
罐子里有你的一切
building everything always they say yes
建立一切，他们总是说是
why we don't know and daya tried to ask
为什么我们不知道，大亚试图问
a conference is why they do this and - I
会议就是他们这样做的原因-我
got one reasonable answer and the answer
得到一个合理的答案，而答案
was all the other jars and fetch ours
是所有其他的罐子，然后拿来我们的
our tent started before Dhaka and before
我们的帐篷在达卡之前和之前开始
Dhaka there was no layering so if you
达卡没有层次感，所以如果您
deploy fetch ours on bare metal without
部署在裸机上获取我们的信息而无需
any of this this perfect so the whites
任何这样的完美，所以白人
fight swarm make sense if you build your
如果您建立自己的团队，那么战斗群是有意义的
complete runtime on bare metal and you
在裸机上完成运行时，您
start Java - charm you think but in the
启动Java-您认为很有魅力，但在
cloud I would like to add the separation
云我想添加分隔
so but I'm a spring boot rookie whatever
所以，但是我是一个春季新秀
trends ask me is Java EE in one
趋势问我Java EE合二为一
particular case they ask me about Java
他们向我询问有关Java的特殊情况
and had actually spring boot but they
并且实际上有弹簧靴，但是他们
were happy at the end and they keep
最后很开心，他们继续
doing spring boot and I could help them
做 spring boot ，我可以帮助他们
because at the end it was Java it was
因为最后是Java
very similar to Java EE the only thing
唯一类似于Java EE的东西
was the deployment was different
部署是否不同
and they started with a main method and
他们从一种主要方法开始
they built their own server this is what
他们建立了自己的服务器，这就是
I can tell you yeah someone else here
我可以告诉你，是这里的其他人
yeah ah we use more and more nothing to
是啊，我们什么也没用
a web web standards and if you have to
Web Web标准，以及是否必须
use something I would use react probably
用我可能会用到的东西
view is nice the problem with view is
视图很好视图的问题是
just one developer so boost factor is a
只是一个开发人员，因此推动因素是
little bit dangerous there and Paulo Mia
那里和Paulo Mia有点危险
is also nice but if you have problem any
也很好，但是如果您有任何问题
question you can always do follow me
问题你总是可以跟着我
afterwards so react is everyone is happy
然后让所有人都感到高兴
I never saw an unhappy react developer
我从未见过一个不高兴的反应开发者
and I never saw a really happy angular
我从没见过真正的快乐
developer if they were not you know
开发商，如果他们不是你知道
functional programming if they didn't
如果没有的话，进行函数式编程
talk about the business logic but they
谈论业务逻辑，但是他们
really like Eric's Jes they talk to how
就像埃里克（Eric）的耶稣（Jes）一样，他们谈论
beauty HTTP dollarized
美HTTP美元化
and I say okay we are fetch all the
我说好吧，我们正在拿走所有
works but here this is different
可以，但是这里不一样
different different opinion you know
你知道不同的不同意见
angular 4 or 5 so my personal opinion is
有角度的4或5，所以我个人的看法是
angular 1 was great and angular 2 is
角度1非常好，角度2非常大
like my opinion so like all the old j2e
就像我的意见一样，就像所有旧的j2e
developers was excellent and so forth
开发人员非常出色，依此类推
quit building service and I'll say we do
退出建筑服务，我会说我们做
the same in the front end and with some
在前端和一些相同
support from OSGi group like modules
OSGi组支持的模块
export in injection and then was so
注射出口然后是
complicated then then they accepted
然后他们接受了
people help out they'll have a
人们会帮助他们
command-line interface to generate a
命令行界面生成一个
view if I would stand sorry we knew you
查看我是否会后悔，我们认识你
need command-line interface to create a
需要命令行界面来创建一个
Java EE component they will never fly
他们永远不会飞的Java EE组件
you will call me crazy but it's absolute
你会叫我疯，但这是绝对的
ok to have a command and interface to
可以有一个命令和界面来
generate a button in a browser now the
现在在浏览器中生成一个按钮
question to you how many files are
问你几个文件
downloaded if you start with angular
如果您从angular开始下载
you start angular you would like to have
你开始想要的角度
hello world on the screen the standard
屏幕上的世界你好标准
way how many fights are download I know
我知道多少次打架
that they show you why in a node modules
他们向您展示了为什么在节点模块中
this informations 1 inc 1 week old
该信息1公司1周大
how many who is 3000 anyone else know
有多少人是3000个其他人都知道
more than application servers 32,000 and
超过32,000个应用服务器和
why I know that because my backup
为什么我知道这是因为我的备份
stopped working and I have to exclude
停止工作，我不得不排除
all the node modules as input impossible
所有节点模块都无法输入
so I have the whole source code from
所以我有完整的源代码
white flag last wish or the service and
白旗最后的愿望或服务和
they do not never the problem and now I
他们从来没有问题，现在我
have a couple of buttons in angular and
在角形上有几个按钮
now everything doesn't work anymore and
现在一切都不再起作用了，
and 32,000 now you get files in node
现在有32,000个节点中的文件
modules if you start with a button and
模块（如果您以按钮开头）和
everyone is happy just like like it's
每个人都快乐，就像
lightweight framework and a bit Java is
轻量级的框架和一点Java是
slow because I saw server which one
慢，因为我看到了服务器中的哪一个
makes a smaller than this right ok any
比这个还小吧
other questions and angular is very
其他问题和角度是非常
popular in Europe and Germany in u.s. is
在欧洲和德国流行的是
going down as it's not like yeah no
下降，因为它不像是的，不
questions then
然后提问
thank you now last question over what no
现在谢谢你关于什么不的最后一个问题
then see you in ten minutes here
十分钟后再见